http://www.microbilt.com/privacy-policy

Home
»
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Our company (“Company”) recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of “Information” about those that visit this website (“Website”) and/or use our products and services. Information, more fully defined below, includes all of the identifying information that you provide to Company, and/or we acquire from your use of this Website and or our products and services. Company is sensitive to your privacy interests and believes that protecting valuable business, personal and financial information is one of Company's most significant responsibilities.
The terms and conditions of the privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) set forth herein, describe Company's policies to protect your privacy, and describe the Information Company collects, and what Company does with it. By using this Website and our products and services, you are consenting to the Information collection and use practices described herein. You agree that Information you submit shall be as complete and accurate as possible. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully before accessing this Website or using any Company product or service. By accessing this Website and/or using the products and services, you confirm that you are over the age of eighteen (18), and you agree to and will be bound by this policy. If you do not agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, please do not use this Website or the products and services.
Privacy Policy
We may collect the following information (all or any portion of which is defined as the “Information”):
We collect personally identifiable information that you provide to us that can identify you such as your name, address, phone number, e-mail address, date of birth and Social Security Number, as well as your user names, passwords, payment, billing, online bank, financial institution, utility companies, landlords, subscriptions, and social media accounts, and transaction history that you may provide to us;
information that you provide to us about other people (such as joint account holders, which with such provision, you confirm you are authorized to provide), including their name, address, phone number, e-mail address, date of birth and Social Security Number;
the name of the Internet service provider and the Internet Protocol (IP) address through which you access the Internet;
the date and time you access the Website;
the pages that you access within the Website and the Internet address of the website from which you linked directly to our Website.
We may at our discretion, use Information to:
manage your customer relationship and provide you with customer support;
research and analyze your use of, or interest in, our products, services and content and the products, services and content offered by others;
communicate with you via e-mail, postal mail, telephone, and/or mobile devices about products or services that may be of interest to you;
develop and display content and services tailored to your interests on our Website and other websites either directly or through our vendors;
develop and deliver targeted advertisements either directly or through our vendors;
measure the overall effectiveness of our online advertising, content, programming and other activities;
perform functions as described to you at the time of collection of the Information;
if applicable, generate a proprietary score and provide such to financial institutions as described herein;
if applicable, furnish such to a financial institution to facilitate a transaction that you may have applied for;
if applicable, match you with financial institutions that may wish to offer products or services to you;
if applicable, verify your identity, protect against or identify possible fraudulent transactions;
if applicable, verify your account information and account history from the accounts you provide to us;
help financial institutions deliver the products and services you may have requested;
store and process such in the United States or any other country in which Company maintains facilities, and by using the Website, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country;
incorporate such into Company’s credit reporting system and use it in accordance with the FCRA and pursuant to your consent provided in this Privacy Policy;
make such accessible through Company’s credit reporting system pursuant to the FCRA by both authorized subscribers and by you and therefore you expressly understand and agree that such Information may be disclosed as permitted by the FCRA and to financial institutions for the purpose of making offers to you;
act in accordance with applicable law.  Company shall have no obligation or responsibility to use, incorporate, or return Information to you or act upon any instructions from you regarding the Information except as expressly set forth hereunder or required by applicable law.  Company reserves the right to exclude the use of certain Information submitted. If Company learns of inaccurately submitted Information, Company reserves the right to update or remove such Information from its credit reporting system.
Retention:
Company retains Information for as long as necessary in accordance with applicable local, state and federal laws regarding use, storage and disclosure of Information, including, but not limited to, the Fair Credit Reporting Act, 15 U.S.C. § 1681 et. seq. (“FCRA”) and the Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act of 1999 (“GLBA”).
All Information voluntarily submitted by you or provided by your accounts pursuant to the access you permit, becomes the property of Company.
You agree that Company may use, retain and/or disclose such Information as set forth herein without financial consideration to you.
Opt Out
If you do not want Company to use, retain and/or disclose your Information as set forth herein, you may opt out by not accessing this Website.
IN THE EVENT YOU WISH CEASE PROVIDING INFORMATION TO US, UPDATE YOUR INFORMATION, OR CORRECT OR DELETE INNACURATE INFORMATION, YOU MAY CONTACT US AS INDICATED HEREIN, OR AS SET FORTH ON THE WEBSITE. HOWEVER, COMPANY WILL RETAIN ACCURATE INFORMATION YOU FURNISHED PRIOR TO YOUR CONTACT, AND THAT WE OBTAINED ABOUT YOU FROM THIRD PARTIES AS DESCRIBED HEREIN AS PERMITTED BY POLICY OR LAW.  YOU MAY REQUEST A COPY OF THE INFORMATION WE OBTAIN AND RETAIN.
Disclaimer
Company does not make any direct, indirect, manual or automated determinations regarding approval of financial transactions for you. If applicable, Company may verify application information and submitted Information, returns such information to the lender (whom makes the approval determination) from whom you may seek a loan and then retains such Information in its credit reporting systems, for use to help you with your future applications for credit at lenders whom use our credit reporting system or services or as otherwise permitted by the FCRA.  A lender may also access your traditional consumer report through us, to which you consent.
Maintenance of Accurate Information
Company has established procedures so that submitted Information is current and complete, in accordance with reasonable commercial standards. Any request to correct inaccurate Information will be responded to within a timely manner.
Company may send out periodic e-mails informing you of technical service or security issues related to a product or service you requested, or confirming you requested a product or service. In some services offered by Company, contact with you may be an intrinsic part of the service. You will not be able to choose to unsubscribe to these mailings, as they may be considered an essential part of the service(s) you have chosen.
Use of Cookies
We may use cookies on this Website to personalize user experiences. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by our web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. For example, if you personalize a web page, or navigate within a website, a cookie helps the website to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of delivering relevant content, eases website navigation, and so on. When you return to the website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the website's features that you customized.
Our Website uses cookies placed by us or our third party vendors for a variety of purposes, including to operate and personalize the Website.
Cookies are used to track how you use our Website, and Company and our third party vendors use cookies to serve ads to you based on your past visits to our Website.  Further, Company and our third party vendors use cookies for remarketing, to serve ads to you on other websites on the Internet.
Our Website uses analytical tools such as Google Analytics, a web analysis service provided by Google, in order to better understand your use of our Website and how we can make improvements, and provide you with more personalized advertisements and optimize your experience with our Website. Google Analytics collects information such as how often users visit a website, what pages you visit when you do so, and what other websites you used prior to coming to such website. Google Analytics collects the IP address assigned to you on the date you visit a website, rather than your name or other identifying information.  Google Analytics provides us with anonymous information collected from other websites which advertise or link to our Website, which enables us to understand how visitors came to and interact with our Website.  We may use this information to enhance or modify our campaigns that are designed to bring visitors to our Website.  We do not combine the information collected through the use of Google Analytics with your personal information. Although Google Analytics plants a permanent cookie on your web browser to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit a website, the cookie cannot be used by anyone but Google. Google’s ability to collect, use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to websites and our Website, and information about your ability to opt-out is governed by Google Analytics Terms of Use located at: https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites, and https://policies.google.com/privacy.
Some Internet browsers allow users to send a "Do Not Track" signal to websites they visit. We do not respond to this signal.  You can opt out of Company’s and our third party vendors’ use of cookies as described herein.
Use of Web Beacons
This Website may contain electronic images known as Web Beacons, sometimes also called single-pixel gifs, which allow Company to count users who have visited those pages and to deliver co-branded services. Company may include Web Beacons in promotional e-mail messages or newsletters in order to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon.
You could accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of this Website or other websites you visit.
Opting-Out From Cookies
We recognize how important your online privacy is to you, so we offer the following options for controlling the targeted ads you receive from us and our third party vendors:
You can opt-out of receiving targeted ads served by us: You can opt out of receiving targeted ads served by us or by others on our behalf contacting us as indicated below. Please note that, if you delete your cookies or upgrade your browser after having opted out, you will need to opt out again. Further, if you use multiple browsers or devices you will need to execute this opt out on each browser or device. If you opt-out we may collect some data about your online activity for operational purposes (such as fraud prevention) but it won't be used for the purpose of targeting ads to you.
You can opt-out of receiving email marketing or targeted ads served by us or our third party vendors: Our third party vendors may be members of the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) and adheres to the NAI Codes of Conduct. You may use the NAI opt out tool here, which will allow you to opt out of seeing targeted ads from us and those of our third party vendor members, and from other NAI approved member companies.
Our third party vendors may also comply with the Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising as managed by the Digital Advertising Alliance (DAA). You may opt out of receiving targeted ads from other companies that perform ad targeting services, including some that our third party vendors may work with as Advertising Partners via the DAA website here.
Our third party vendors may also comply with the Canadian Self-regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising as managed by the Digital Advertising Alliance of Canada (DAAC). If and as applicable to you, you may opt out of receiving targeted ads from other companies that perform ad targeting services, including some that our third party vendors may work with as Advertising Partners via the DAAC website here.
Our third party vendors may also adhere to the European Interactive Advertising Digital Alliance (EDAA) guidelines for online advertising. If and as applicable to you, you may opt out via their website Your Online Choices.
Limiting Employee Access to Information
All Company employees are educated about the importance of privacy and confidentiality. Only those employees having a legitimate business reason for knowing submitted Information have access to such.
Updates to this Privacy Policy
Company reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, with or without notice. Any modifications will become effective immediately upon posting to this Website. You agree that it is your responsibility to visit the Website and review the Privacy Policy periodically to be aware of such modifications, as your continued access or use of this Website shall be deemed your conclusive acceptance of the modified Privacy Policy.
Termination
Company shall have the right to terminate, discontinue, suspend or modify this Website, the products or services at any time, in whole or in part, with or without notice, at Company’s sole discretion and you agree that Company shall have no liability for doing so. In addition, Company may, in its sole discretion, refuse or restrict its products or services to anyone at any time. Further, Company reserves the right to investigate, involve and cooperate with appropriate investigatory departments or authorities regarding any suspected or actual fraudulent or other illegal or unauthorized activities involving this Website, products or services and to disclose any information necessary for such purpose.
Ownership and Trademarks
This Website, products and services, including all content, HTML, source, object or other code, pages, wording, marks, names graphics, software and all other materials associated with or within this Website (collectively, the "Content"), and the compilation of the Content and the "look and feel" of this Website, products and services are the property of Company and its licensors and service providers, and protected by US and international copyright and intellectual property rights laws and treaties. No portion of the Content may be used or exploited for any purpose and in any form without the express prior written permission of Company and as applicable, its licensors and service providers.
The Company names, logos, marks, product and service names are trademarks or registered trademarks of Company and Company's property, which may not be used for any purpose without the express prior written permission of Company. Other names and marks used on this Website are the property of the respective owners. All rights not expressly granted are reserved.
Disclaimer of Warranties
THE WEBSITE, SERVICES AND PRODUCTS THEREIN ARE PROVIDED TO YOU ON AN "AS IS" AND "AS AVAILABLE" BASIS AND ALL WARRANTIES, EXPRESS AND IMPLIED, ARE DISCLAIMED TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMISSIBLE PURSUANT TO APPLICABLE LAW (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE DISCLAIMER OF ANY WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, NON-INFRINGEMENT OF INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY AND/OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE). IN PARTICULAR, BUT NOT AS A LIMITATION THEREOF, COMPANY MAKES NO WARRANTY THAT: (A) THE WEBSITE, PRODUCTS OR SERVICES WILL MEET YOUR REQUIREMENTS: (B) THE WEBSITE, PRODUCTS OR SERVICES WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED, CONTINUOUS, TIMELY, SECURE OR ERROR-FREE; OR (C) THE RESULTS THAT MAY BE OBTAINED FROM THE USE OF THE WEBSITE, PRODUCTS, OR SERVICES WILL BE ACCURATE OR RELIABLE. THE WEBSITE, PRODUCTS OR SERVICES MAY CONTAIN BUGS, ERRORS, PROBLEMS OR OTHER LIMITATIONS. COMPANY WILL NOT BE LIABLE FOR THE AVAILABILITY OF THE UNDERLYING INTERNET CONNECTION ASSOCIATED WITH THE WEBSITE, PRODUCTS OR SERVICES. NO ADVICE OR INFORMATION, WHETHER ORAL OR WRITTEN, OBTAINED BY YOU FROM COMPANY OR THROUGH OR FROM THE WEBSITE, PRODUCTS OR SERVICES SHALL CREATE ANY WARRANTY NOT EXPRESSLY STATED HEREIN.
Limitation of Liability
YOU EXPRESSLY UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT COMPANY SHALL NOT BE LIABLE TO YOU OR ANY THIRD PARTY FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, CONSEQUENTIAL AND/OR EXEMPLARY DAMAGES INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PERSONAL INJURY OR DEATH, DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF PROFITS, GOODWILL, USE, DATA OR OTHER INTANGIBLE LOSSES (EVEN IF COMPANY HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES), TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMISSIBLE BY LAW FOR: (A) ANY COMMUNICATION LINE, COMPUTER, SYSTEM, INTERNET, SERVER, EQUIPMENT, SOFTWARE OR E-MAIL FAILURE, MALFUNCTION, ERROR, OMISSION, INTERRUPTION, DELETION, DEFECT, DELAY IN OPERATION OR TRANSMISSION; (B) THE USE OR THE INABILITY TO USE THE WEBSITE, OR ANY PRODUCT AND/OR SERVICE OFFERED VIA THE WEBSITE; (C) ANY MATTER RELATING TO ANY PROMOTIONS THAT MAY BE AVAILABLE VIA THE WEBSITE; (D) THE COST OF PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS AND SERVICES RESULTING FROM ANY PROBLEM(S) WITH THE GOODS, DATA, INFORMATION AND/OR SERVICES PURCHASED OR OBTAINED FROM THE WEBSITE, OR TRANSACTIONS ENTERED INTO, THROUGH OR FROM THE WEBSITE; OR (E) THE UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS TO, OR ALTERATION OF, YOUR SUBMITTED INFORMATION. THIS LIMITATION APPLIES TO ALL CAUSES OF ACTION, IN THE AGGREGATE INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, BREACH OF CONTRACT, BREACH OF WARRANTY, NEGLIGENCE, STRICT LIABILITY, MISREPRESENTATIONS, AND ANY AND ALL OTHER TORTS. YOU HEREBY RELEASE COMPANY, AND ITS SUPPLIERS, FROM ANY AND ALL OBLIGATIONS, LIABILITIES, AND CLAIMS IN EXCESS OF THE LIMITATIONS STATED HEREUNDER. IF APPLICABLE LAW DOES NOT PERMIT SUCH LIMITATIONS, THE MAXIMUM LIABILITY OF COMPANY TO YOU UNDER ANY AND ALL CIRCUMSTANCES WILL BE EQUAL TO THE AMOUNTS YOU PAID, IF ANY, FOR ANY PRODUCTS AND/OR SERVICES. YOU HEREBY RELEASE COMPANY FROM ANY AND ALL OBLIGATIONS, LIABILITIES AND CLAIMS IN EXCESS OF THE LIMITATIONS SET FORTH IN THIS SECTION. THE NEGATION OF DAMAGES SET FORTH ABOVE IS A FUNDAMENTAL ELEMENT OF THE BASIS OF THE BARGAIN BETWEEN YOU AND COMPANY. THE WEBSITE, PRODUCTS AND SERVICES WOULD NOT BE PROVIDED TO YOU WITHOUT SUCH LIMITATIONS.
Legal Warning
Any attempt by any individual accessing this Website, the products, or services, to damage, destroy, tamper with, vandalize and/or otherwise interfere with the operation of the Website, products or services, is a violation of criminal and civil law and Company will diligently pursue any and all remedies in this regard against any offending individual or entity to the fullest extent permissible by law and in equity. You agree not to use this Website to engage in any prohibited conduct or for any unlawful purpose. Broadly stated, this includes any conduct that is unlawful, untruthful, tortious or that is harmful to (or puts at risk) Company or any other party or property; that violates another party's privacy or other rights; or that otherwise interferes with the operation, use or enjoyment of this Website or any product, service, system or other property. Further, you agree to submit only true, valid and accurate Information to this Website (including through any registration or application process). You also agree to correct promptly any errors in any Information related to you. You may not use this Website to seek to discover or obtain information about, or to provide information about, any other person or entity unless you have the explicit legal right to do so.
No part of the Website, products, or services may be reproduced in any form or incorporated into any information retrieval system, electronic or mechanical. You may not use, copy, emulate, clone, rent, lease, sell, modify, decompile, disassemble, reverse engineer or transfer the products, services, Website, Website content or any portion thereof. Systematic retrieval of content or matter associated with the Website by automated means or any other form of scraping or data extraction in order to create or compile, directly or indirectly, a collection, compilation, database or directory without written permission from Company is strictly prohibited. You may not use any device, software or routine to interfere or attempt to interfere with the proper functionality of the Website. You may not take any action that imposes an unreasonable or disproportionately large load on Company infrastructure.
Resolution of Claims and Disputes; Arbitration
We will try work in good faith to resolve any issue you have with this Website and the products and services available hereunder, if you timely bring the issue to our attention. However, we realize that there may be rare cases when we may not be able to resolve an issue to your complete satisfaction. In those instances, you agree that any dispute or claim arising out of or relating in any way to your use of this Website and the products and services available hereunder, must be resolved exclusively by binding arbitration. The only exception would be if you have violated or threatened to violate the intellectual property rights of Company or any third party, in which case Company, or such third party may go to court to seek an injunction or other appropriate relief.
The arbitration will be conducted before a single arbitrator in accordance with the rules of the American Arbitration Association (“AAA”). No claims of any other parties may be joined or otherwise combined in the arbitration proceeding. In other words, you agree that you will not be allowed to file a class action or any kind of class or joint arbitration regarding Company, this Website and the products and services available hereunder.
Each party is responsible for its own attorneys’ fees without regard to which party is deemed the prevailing party in the arbitration proceeding. Except for punitive and consequential damages (which the arbitrator is not authorized to award), and subject to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, the arbitrator is authorized to award either party any money damages or any provisional or equitable remedy permitted by applicable law.
The award of the arbitrator may be enforced by the prevailing party in any court having jurisdiction. Each party consents to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts of the State of New Jersey or to any Federal court located within the State of New Jersey for any action (i) to compel arbitration, (ii) to enforce any award of the arbitrators, or (iii) at any time prior to the qualification and appointment of the arbitrator, for temporary, interim, or provisional equitable remedies.
If this arbitration provision is held to be invalid or otherwise unenforceable for any reason, it will be severed from this Privacy Policy and the parties agree that exclusive jurisdiction and venue for any claims will be in the state or federal courts in New Jersey.
You agree that, even if a statute of limitations or other law provides for a longer time period, any action against Company, their officers, directors, shareholders, employees, attorneys, agents, contractors, licensors, suppliers and any third party providers of information, products, or services relating to this Website or any information, products, or services available on or from this Website must be brought within twelve (12) months after the event that gave rise to the cause of action or it is forever barred.
BECAUSE YOUR USE OF THIS WEBSITE REQUIRES THAT YOU CONSENT TO ARBITRATION OF YOUR CLAIMS OR DISPUTES, YOU WILL NOT HAVE THE RIGHT TO PURSUE YOUR CLAIM IN COURT OR BEFORE A JUDGE OR JURY OR TO PARTICIPATE IN A CLASS ACTION OR ANY OTHER COLLECTIVE OR REPRESENTATIVE PROCEEDING. THE ARBITRATOR'S DECISION WILL BE FINAL AND BINDING. OTHER RIGHTS THAT EITHER PARTY WOULD HAVE IF THAT PARTY WENT TO COURT, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION THE RIGHT TO CONDUCT DISCOVERY OR TO APPEAL, MAY BE LIMITED OR UNAVAILABLE IN ARBITRATION. IF ANY COURT WERE TO FIND THAT THIS ARBITRATION CLAUSE WERE UNENFORCEABLE FOR ANY REASON, THEN YOU AGREE TO PURSUE YOUR CLAIM EXCLUSIVELY IN A STATE OR FEDERAL COURT IN NEW JERSEY AND AGREE THAT A JUDGE RATHER THAN A JURY IS TO ADJUDICATE YOUR CLAIM.
Miscellaneous
This Privacy Policy shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the sole and exclusive law, jurisdiction and venue of the State of New Jersey (without regard to its conflict of law principles) and may not be assigned by you in whole or in part without the prior written consent of Company.
Notices by you to Company must be in writing and sent by US Mail or overnight delivery to MicroBilt, 1640 Airport Road, Suite 115, Kennesaw, GA 30144, unless revised by Company in writing.
Performance by Company may be subject to interruption and delay due to causes beyond its reasonable control, such as acts of God, government, weather, fire, power or telecommunications failure, inability to obtain supplies, breakdown of equipment or interruption in utility company, landlord, lender, bank, financial institution or vendor services or communications, for which no liability shall be incurred.
Should any part of this Privacy Policy be held invalid or unenforceable, that portion shall be replaced by an enforceable provision consistent with applicable law that most closely matches the intent of the original provision and the remaining portions of this Privacy Policy shall continue in full force and effect. Section headings used in this Privacy Policy are for convenience purposes only.
This Privacy Policy represents the entire understanding between you and Company regarding the subject matter contained herein and supersedes any and all prior and/or contemporaneous agreements between you and Company regarding same, whether oral or written. Company’s failure to enforce any provision of this Privacy Policy shall not be deemed a waiver of such provision nor of the right to enforce such provision.
Company shall have, in addition to any other relief at law or in equity, the right to injunctive relief to redress any breach of this Privacy Policy.
This Privacy Policy is intended for the benefit of, is binding upon and may be enforced solely by you and Company, their successors and permitted assigns. This Privacy Policy does not create, and you and Company expressly disclaim, any third-party beneficiary relationships.
Acknowledgement and Acceptance
BY ACCESSING THIS WEBSITE AND THE PRODUCTS AND SERVICES HEREIN, YOU AGREE, ACKNOWLEDGE AND CONSENT THAT THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS ON ALL PAGES OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY HAVE BEEN THOROUGHLY READ, UNDERSTOOD AND AGREED TO, INCLUDING THE ARBITRATION CLAUSE CONTAINED HEREIN. YOU FURTHER AGREE, ACKNOWLEDGE AND CONSENT THAT YOU HAVE INDEPENDENTLY EVALUATED AND WEIGHED THE RISKS AND BENEFITS OF ACCESSING THIS WEBSITE AND THE PRODUCTS AND SERVICES HEREIN AND YOU HAVE AGREED TO ALL THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY WITHOUT RELIANCE ON ANY REPRESENTATION, GUARANTEE OR STATEMENT EXISTING OUTSIDE OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY. YOUR ACCESS TO THIS WEBSITE AND THE PRODUCTS AND SERVICES HEREIN, SHALL CONSTITUTE YOUR LEGAL, VALID AND BINDING MARK, WITH THE SAME FORCE AND EFFECT AS A PHYSICALLY SIGNED ORIGINAL, AND REPRESENTS YOUR AGREEMENT, ACKNOWLEDGEMENT AND CONSENT TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND TO THE ELECTRONIC DELIVERY AND ACCEPTANCE THEREOF AND ALL EXHIBITS, DOCUMENTS, NOTICES, UPDATES, ADDENDA AND AMENDMENTS RELATED THERETO, AS WELL AS ANY OTHER DOCUMENTS TO BE DELIVERED TO YOU AS A RESULT OF YOUR ACCESS AND USE OF THE WEBSITE, PRODUCTS AND SERVICES.
It is acknowledged that this Privacy Policy may exist in multiple counterparts, each of which shall be deemed an original and all of which together shall constitute one and the same instrument. You understand that you will need access to the Internet, as well as the appropriate software and/or programs, which may include, but may not be limited to, Adobe Acrobat, in order to access this Privacy Policy electronically. You also understand that you may update your information, obtain a full description of systems requirements, revoke your consent for future electronic deliveries, or request one or more paper documents at any time by contacting Company in writing.
Information subject to change without notice.
All rights reserved. ©
MicroBilt
Speak with a business solution consultant
We’re here to help you protect and grow your business. If you have questions or need help let us know.
Online Chat
Call Me
Security Center
Security is our top priority. Learn more about how we are taking an active role in protecting you from security risks.
About
News & Resources
Contact Us
Partnership Programs
Employee Entrance
Careers
Legal Notice
Privacy Policy
Laws & Notices
End User Agreement
Addendums
Consumer Affairs
Consumer credit reports must be used for permissible purposes only. Unauthorized access is a crime and may result in federal prosecution. Customers are required to retain supporting documentation for each transaction.
MicroBilt Corp is a registered ISO of Synovus Bank, Columbus, Georgia.
© MicroBilt Corporation 2020. All Rights Reserved
×
Thank you for inquiring about MicroBilt
